An Inventory of the United States. Food Administration records XX066
Hoover Institution Archives
- 27-H Dr. Vernon L. Kellogg, Representative in Europe files, 1917-1918. (Folder 68)
  See also 17-H
  - Mary A. Coit, memoranda and correspondence, 1918 (Folder 68: 7)
  - "Memorandum of Correspondence Received in Regard to Food Situation in Europe," nos. 1-19, 1918-1919 (Folder 68: 8-9)
  - "Weekly Survey of Foreign Food Situation," special reports, May-August, 1918 (Folder 68: 10)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 68: 11-19)
  - Printed matter, 1918 (Folder 68: 19)
- 28-H Supply Division records, 1917-1919 (Folder 68)
  - Reports of operations, by Chief of Division B. F. Durr, 1918-1919 (Folder 69: 1-3)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 69: 4)
  - Requisitions, 1917-1919 (Folder 69: 5-9)
- 29-H Food Purchase Board records, 1915-1922 (Folder 69)
  - Frederic S. Snyder, Chief of Meat Division, reports, 1917-1922. (Folder 69: 10-11)
  - Army and Navy contracts, exhibits 1-10, 1917-1922 (Folder 69: 12-13)
  - Admiral Samuel McGowan, Navy contracts, 1915-1918 (Folder 69: 14-15)
- 30-H Sugar Division records, 1917-1923, 1942. (Folder 69)
  See also 46-H; 48-H, Alphabetical file, Great Britain, USFA, Correspondence, George Jackson (Royal Commission on the Sugar Supply)
  - Chief of Division George M. Rolph, 1917-1919 (Folder 69)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, 1917-1918 (Folder 69: 16-18)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 69: 1-5)
    - Brief Preliminary Report; periods August 1917 to May, 1918, 25 June 1918 (Folder 70: 6)
  - Office correspondence, reports, 1917-1920 (Folder 70: 7-19)
  - Agreements, 1917-1918 (Folder 70: 20-21)
  - Report of the Committee on Cane Syrup and Molasses to the Honorable Herbert Hoover, 1918 (Folder 70: 1)
  - International Sugar Committee, 1917-1918 (Folder 71: 2)
  - Regulations and Conservation Measures, 1917-1918 (Folder 71: 3-10)
  - Statistics, 1915-1918 (Folder 71: 11-15)
  - Charts and maps, 1917-1919 (Folder 71: 16-18)
  - Confidential Report to Herbert Hoover, Outline Statement on Sugar Situation, July-September 1918 (Folder 71: 1)
  - Correspondence with sugar brokers, 1917-1918, 1923 (Folder 72)
    - The A. H. Lamborn Co., 1917-1918 (Folder 72: 2-4)
    - The American Sugar Refining Company, Earl D. Babst, 1917-1918 (Folder 72: 5)
    - Federal Sugar Refining Company, Claus A. Spreckels and Frank A. Lowry, 1917-1918, 1923 (Folder 72: 6-7)
    - Revere Sugar Refinery, Dwight P. Thomas, 1917 (Folder 72: 8)
  - Reports, 1917-1918, 1942 (Folder 72)
    - The Sugar Situation, by A. L. Mathews, Vice-President, J. G. White Management Corporation, 1917 (Folder 72: 9)
    - Sugar, Policies and Plan of Operation, by Charles Merz, May 1918 (Folder 72: 10)
    - Sugar Investigation.
      See Alphabetical file, Sugar, Sugar Shortage Investigation
    - Control of the Sugar Market during World War I, by Enoch Needham and Stella Stewart, March 1942 (Folder 72: 11)
    - Sugar Rationing in 1918, by Stella Stewart and Irving Bernstein, January 1942 (Folder 72: 12)
- 31-H Transportation Division records, 1917-1919. (Folder 72-73)
  See also 36-H
  - Edward Chambers, C. E. Spens, F. S. Brooks, C. E. Bell, and P. W. Davis, 1917-1918 (Folder 72: 13-18)
  - Bartlett Frazier, 1918 (Folder 72: 19)
  - Regulations, 1981-1919 (Folder 73: 1)
- 32-H Heads of Departments records, 1917-1919. (Folder 73)
  See also 10-H, Alphabetical file, Personnel, Salaries
  - Major James Miles, Office Manager, 1917-1919 (Folder 73: 2-7)
  - Captain J. F. Lucey, memoranda "All Departments,", 1917 (Folder 73: 8)
  - Clinton R. Whitney, Chief clerk, office memoranda, 1917-1918 (Folder 73: 9-11)
  - Frederick P. Champ, Messenger and Office Service Section and automobiles, 1917-1918 (Folder 73: 12)
  - H. M. Brown, travel and transportation of personnel, 1917-1918 (Folder 73: 13)
  - Douglas Kellogg, W. E. Groome, Telegraph Division, 1917-1919 (Folder 73: 14-15)
  - Telephone Division, 1918 (Folder 73: 16)
  - Liberty Loan Committee, 1917-1918 (Folder 73: 17)
- 33-H Labor and Consumers' Interests Division records, 1917-1918 (Folder 73-74)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 73: 18-20)
  - The Bread Problem in the Food Administration, report to Samuel Gompers, President of American Federation of Labor, March 1918 (Folder 73: 21)
  - The Bread Problem and the Consumer, report by the Consumers' Committee, 17 October 1917 (Folder 73: 22)
  - Flour at $5.75 through a Federal Subsidy, report by Ellis, Le Clerc, and Surface, 1918 (Folder 73: 23)
  - American Federation of Labor, Samuel Gompers, 1918 (Folder 74: 1)
  - War Labor Policies Board, M. B. Hammond, Felix Frankfurter, 1918-1919 (Folder 74: 2)
- 34-H Dairy Division records, 1917 (Folder 74)
  - George E. Haskell, Director, 1917. (Folder 74: 3)
    See also 35-H
  - Confidential Documents on Milk Situation When Handled by Mark L. Requa, report by H. L. Gutterson, 1917 (Folder 74: 4)
- 35-H Perishable Food Division records, 1917-1922 (Folder 74)
  - G. Harold Powell, Director, 1917-1922 (Folder 74: 5-8)
  - Dairy and Poultry Coordination and Policy Board, minutes of meetings, 16 October - 13 November 1918 (Folder 74: 9)
  - Fish, Fruit, and Vegetable Coordination and Policy Board, minutes of meeting, 31 October 1918 (Folder 74: 10)
  - Perishables, Policies and Plan of Operation, April 1918 (Folder 74: 11)
  - H. J. Eustace, correspondence, 1918-1919 (Folder 74: 12)
  - Cold storage [transferred to Meat Division (15-H) in October 1918], 1917-1920. (Folder 74: 13-16)
    See also boxes 31 and 478
  - Dairy production, reports, 1918 (Folder 74: 17-18)
  - The Dairy and the World Food Problem, address by Herbert Hoover at the National Milk and Dairy Farm Exposition, New York City, May 23, 1918 (Folder 75: 1)
  - Weekly reports on dairy products, 1918-1919 (Folder 75: 2)
  - Rules and regulations, 1918-1919 (Folder 75: 3-4)
  - Milk prices limitation, Judge William E. Lamb, 1917-1918 (Folder 75: 5-8)
  - The Production, Distribution and Food Value of Milk, Report to Herbert C. Hoover by the Milk Committee, 1918 (Folder 75: 9)
  - Report on organization and operation of the Milk Producers Association, Chicago district, 1917 (Folder 75: 10)
  - Condensed milk, regulations and reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 75: 11-12)
  - War Trade Board, Bureau of Research, Fishing industry, correspondents and reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 75: 13-17)
  - Kenneth Fowler, fisheries regulations and reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 75: 18-19)
  - Lou D. Sweet, potato campaign, 1917-1918 (Folder 76: 1-3)
  - W. F. Priebe, poultry and eggs, 1917-1918 (Folder 76: 4)
  - Dean H. L. Russell, agricultural activities, 1917-1918 (Folder 76: 5)
- 36-H Marine Transportation Division records, 1918-1919, 1935 (Folder 76)
  - Prentiss N. Gray, memoranda, correspondence, 1918-1919, 1935 (Folder 76: 6-8)
  - Anglo-Norwegian Shipping Agency, Inc., 1918-1919 (Folder 76: 9)
  - J. D. Fletcher, correspondence, 1918-1919 (Folder 76: 10-12)
  - Coffee transportation, 1918-1919 (Folder 76: 13)
  - Birt & Co., Ltd., Sydney, correspondence, 1918-1919 (Folder 76: 14-15)
- 37-H License Division of Law Department records, 1917-1918, 1941. (Folder 76)
  See also 40-H
  - William B. Owens, Director, 1917-1918 (Folder 76: 16)
  - General and Special License Regulations arranged by subject, nos. I-XXVII, 1917-1918 (Folder 77-78)
  - General and Special License Regulations arranged by subject, nos. I-XXVII, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 79: 1)
  - Interpretations and rulings, 1917 (Folder 79: 2)
  - Special rules and regulations, 1917-18 (Folder 79: 3-7)
  - Special License Regulations, nos. III-XXV, 1918 (Folder 79: 8-9)
  - Memoranda, 1918 (Folder 79: 10)
  - Applications for license, forms, and instructions, 1917-1918 (Folder 79: 11)
  - Importance of Powers to License Industry as an Aid to Price Control, by Stella Stewart, September 1941 (Folder 79: 12)
- 38-H Cottonseed Industry Division records, 1917-1920. (Folder 79)
  See also 42-H
  - George H. Denny, 1918-1919 (Folder 79: 13)
  - Hugh Humphreys, 1917-1918 (Folder 79: 14)
  - S. J. Cassels and T. F. Justiss, 1918-1920 (Folder 79: 15)
  - Correspondence, 1918-1920 (Folder 79: 16)
  - Memoranda, 1918-1919 (Folder 79: 17)
  - Statistical reports, 1917-1919 (Folder 79: 18)
  - Press releases, 1918 (Folder 79: 19)
  - Special licenses, rules, and regulations, 1917-1920 (Folder 80: 1-2)
- 39-H Chemicals, Sisal, and Jute Division records (also known as Collateral Commodities Division, established 14 May 1918), 1917-1919 (Folder 80)
  - Charles W. Merrill, R. E. Cranston, Henry Wolfer and W. H. Campbell, 1917-1919 (Folder 80: 3-5)
  - Ammonia production, regulations, and reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 80: 6-7)
  - Inter-Department Ammonia Committee, 1917-1918 (Folder 80: 8)
  - Conferences on ammonia, arsenic, ice, and soft corn alcohol, 1917-1918 (Folder 80: 9-10)
  - Inter-Department Glycerin Committee, 1918 (Folder 80: 11)
  - Coordination and Policy Board, minutes of meetings, 1918 (Folder 80: 12)
  - Sisal, jute, and binder twine, 1917-1918 (Folder 80: 13-15)
- 40-H License Reports Division records, 1917-1918 (Folder 80-81)
  - William E. Kellicott, Director, 1917-1918. (Folder 80: 16)
    Includes lists of Total Licenses by States and Commodities Divisions
  - Reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 80: 17-19)
  - Reports, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 81: 1-2)
- 41-H Garbage (Waste) Utilization Department records, 1917-1919 (Folder 81)
  - Irvin S. Osborn, F.C. Bamman, correspondence, reports, and charts, 1917-1919 (Folder 81: 3-4)
- 42-H Fats and Oils Division records, 1917-1919. (Folder 81)
  See also 58-H
  - B. E. Reuter, 1917-1918 (Folder 81: 5-6)
  - Regulations, 1918-1919 (Folder 81: 7)
- 43-H Hotels and Restaurants Division records, 1917-1919 (Folder 81)
  1941
  - John M. Bowman, Director, and W. A. McKenzie, 1917-1918 (Folder 81: 8-10)
  - Executive Assistant Albert S. Crockett, correspondence, reports, and memoranda, 1917-1918 (Folder 81: 11-12)
  - Hotel, Restaurant, Dining Car, and Steamship Division, history by Albert Stevens Crockett, December, 1917 (Folder 81: 13-14)
  - Paul B. Boden, 1917-1918 (Folder 82: 1)
  - General reports on hotel restaurants in Baltimore, Philadelphia, New York, Boston, Norfolk, Charleston, Savannah, and Richmond, 1917, by John P. Sterling (Folder 82: 2)
  - Steamship Department, Edward R. Grabow, 1917-1918 (Folder 82: 3)
  - Regulations, 1918-1919 (Folder 82: 4-5)
- 44-H Enforcement Division records, 1917-1920 (Folder 82-86)
  - William D. Eaton, 1919-1920 (Folder 82: 6-7)
  - Alan Fox, 1919 (Folder 82: 8)
  - Roland W. Boyden, Director, 1917-1919 (Folder 82: 9-13)
  - First Criminal Prosecution Under Food Act, memoranda to All Federal Food Administrators, 27 September, 1918 (Folder 82: 14)
  - Chief of Investigating Department Lawrence Richey, reports, 1919-1920. (Folder 83: 1-3)
    Includes regulations, printed matter, and uniform emblems and pins
  - Investigations, cases, penalties, 1917-1920 (Folder 83)
    - Baltimore Pearl Hominy Company, 1918-1920 (Folder 83: 4)
    - Beans, 1917-1919 (Folder 83)
      - Roland W. Boyden's preliminary report, circa 1918 (Folder 83: 5)
      - Benjamin Moritz's report, 1919 (Folder 83: 6)
      - Testimony of K. P. Kimball and B. Gerks, 1919 (Folder 83: 7)
      - Relationship between the Michigan Bean Co. of Port Huron, Michigan, its General Manager A. L. Chamberlain, and the Grain Corporation of New York, by A. L. Chamberlain, 1919 (Folder 83: 8)
      - The Kimball-Martindale Co. transactions, 1919 (Folder 83: 9)
      - Penal laws of the United States, circa 1919 (Folder 83: 10)
      - "Alan Fox's Memorandum for Mr. Barnes, re Mr. Hoar,", 22 March 1919 (Folder 83: 11)
      - Approved Statement of Conclusions of California Representatives, 14 February 1919 (Folder 83: 12)
      - Diary of Work on Bean Investigation, 1919 (Folder 83: 13)
      - Conference, 30 January 1919 (Folder 83: 14)
      - Correspondence, statements, and reports, 1918-1919 (Folder 83: 15-18)
      - Kutner matters, Alan Fox file on Kutner, 1918-1919 (Folder 83: 19)
      - Kutner Cables to and from the Orient, 1918-1919 (Folder 84: 1)
      - Kutner contracts; valuable evidence, 1917-1919 (Folder 84: 2-4)
      - Western Import Co., Mr. Barnes' file, 1918-1919 (Folder 84: 5)
      - Memorandum on cancellation of Kutner contracts, 1919 (Folder 84: 6)
      - Investigative papers of Kutner contracts, 1918 (Folder 84: 7-8)
      - Lewis E. Sands, Sands' evidence report on L. E. Sands Co. and Bean Storage Corporation, 1918-1919 (Folder 84: 9-10)
      - Relations, Sands and Kutner, 1918 (Folder 84: 11)
      - W. A. Jackson report, 1919 (Folder 84: 12)
      - L. Richey's papers brought back from Albion, New York, 1918-1919 (Folder 84: 13-14)
      - Report of Investigation of Bean Transactions of Grain Corporation, 25 April 1919 (Folder 84)
        - Part I General Resume (Folder 84: 15)
        - Part II Eutner (Folder 84: 16)
        - Part III Sands (Folder 85: 1)
        - Part IV Moritz (Folder 85: 2)
        - Transmittal letters, 1919 (Folder 85: 3)
      - Report of H. Ruple on Profits Received by the Lewis E. Sands Company on Sales to the Grain Corporation, 24 April 1919 (Folder 85: 4)
      - Percent of Jobbing Profits of a Michigan Bean and Grain Jobber for the Year Ending, 1916 (Folder 85: 5)
      - Testimony of Lewis E. Sands, Ben Gerks, Kenneth P. Kimball, Carl P. Buckland, Benjamin Moritz, Abe L. Kutner and others, New York, 6 February - 11 March 1919 (Folder 85: 6-15)
    - Coffee, G. W. Lawrence, 1918-1919 (Folder 86: 1)
    - Globe Grain and Milling Company, 1919 (Folder 86: 2)
    - Miscellaneous cases, 1918 (Folder 86: 3)
    - North Packing and Provision Company, Somerville, Massachusetts, 1919 (Folder 86: 4)
    - Porto Rico case [Padilla against Albert E. Lee, the Food Administrator of the state], 1918 (Folder 86: 5)
    - Rejection cases, suggested procedures, 1918 (Folder 86: 6)
    - Saginaw Milling Company, 1920 (Folder 86: 7)
    - Topeka Flour Mills, 1919 (Folder 86: 8)
    - Letters of appreciation, Roland W. Boyden, 1918-1919 (Folder 86: 9)
    - Alfred Brandeis and John C. Miller, Milling Division, correspondence, statements, and reports, 1917-1919 (Folder 86: 10-11)
    - New Cereal Division-Relations between Enforcement Division and Federal Food Administrators, memorandum, 29 July 1918 (Folder 86: 12)
    - Official Statement of the U.S. Food Administration, 6 June 1918 (Folder 86: 13)
- 45-H Ray Lyman Wilbur, Chief of Food Conservation files, 1917-1919 (Folder 86)
  - Columbia University lectures on Food Administration, 1918 (Folder 86: 14-15)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 86)
    - General A-Z, 1917-1918 (Folder 86: 16-18)
    - California A-Z, 1917-1918 (Folder 86: 19-22)
    - Everett Colby, 1918-1919 (Folder 87: 1)
    - Everett W. Smith, 1918-1919 (Folder 87: 2)
    - Edith Guerrier, 1918-1919 (Folder 87: 3)
    - Lily C. McFadden, 1917-1918 (Folder 87: 4)
    - Inter-office, 1917-1919 (Folder 87: 5-9)
  - Address at the Palace Hotel, San Francisco, 22 November 1918 (Folder 87: 10)
- 46-H Sugar and Flour Distribution records, 1918-1919 (Folder 87)
  - George A. Zabriskie, President of Sugar Equalization Board, 1918-1919 (Folder 87: 11)
- 47-H Commercial Baking Division records, 1917-1919 (Folder 87)
  - Bread, baking, and bakers, 1917-1918. (Folder 87: 12-13)
    See also Alphabetical file, Federal Trade Commission and 10-H
  - Duncan McDuffie, Director, 1917-1918 (Folder 87: 14)
  - Report on the Commercial Baking Problem, November 1917 (Folder 87: 15)
  - Report of the Federal Trade Commission on Bakery Business in the United States, November 1917 (Folder 87: 16)
  - Preliminary Report on Bread Investigation, 29 September 1917 (Folder 87: 17)
  - A. I. Esberg, Director, 1917-1918 (Folder 87: 18)
  - Benjamin R. Jacobs, 1917-1918 (Folder 88: 1-2)
  - General Considerations Relating to the Importance of the Bread Ration in the Diet of the People, the Conservation of Bread Grains, and Prevention of Waste in the same, report, 15 June 1927 (Folder 88: 3)
  - Regulations, 1917-1919 (Folder 88: 4-6)
  - Tariff Commission, Commission of Inquiry into the Milling Division, 1918.
    See Alphabetical file; Tariff Commission
- 48-H Sugar Equalization Board records, 1918-1919 (Folder 88)
  - Memorandum on H. Hoover's views as to steps to be taken with regard to sugar control "during the next few months," 5 July 1918 (Folder 88: 7)
- Alphabetical file, 1901-1928, 1940-1942 (Folder 88-203,300-315, 420)
  See also boxes 300-315, 420
  - A correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 88: 8-16)
  - A correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 89: 1-4)
  - Accounting., See 19-H
  - Ackerly, Dana T., See 21-H
  - Advertising., See 12-H
  - Africa, exports and imports, 1918 (Folder : 5-7)
  - Agricultural Advisory Committee, 1918-1920 (Folder 89)
  - Chairman, Governor Henry C. Stuart, 1918-1920 (Folder 89-90: 8-11)
    - First Meeting, 28 March - 3 April 1918 (Folder 89)
    - Reports, recommendations, and statements from the Food Administration (Folder 89: 12)
    - Rules of procedures (Folder 89: 13)
    - Rules of procedures (contd.) (Folder 89: 1-2)
    - Stenographic reports (Folder 90: 3-5)
    - Minutes, 30 March 1918 (Folder 90: 6)
    - Second Meeting, 27 June - 2 July 1918 (Folder 90)
    - Stenographic reports (Folder 90: 7)
    - Abstracts of fourth and fifth days (Folder 90: 8)
    - Resolutions and reports of Sub-Committees (Folder 90: 9)
    - Report of Discussions on the Licensing and Elimination Program for Agricultural Implements (Folder 90: 10)
    - Report of Commission of Inquiry into the Milling Division, June 1918 (Folder 90: 11)
    - Third Meeting, 5-8 August 1918 (Folder 90)
    - Minutes (Folder 90: 12)
    - Resolutions, reports of sub-committees (Folder 90: 13)
    - Persons appearing before the Agricultural Advisory Committee, report, 1918 (Folder 90: 14)
    - Livestock Committee, 3 April - 26 October 1918 (Folder 90: 15)
    - Meat Policies Committee, 3-29 May 1918 (Folder 90: 16)
    - Press notices, 1918 (Folder 90: 17)
    - Agricultural implements, 1918. (Folder 90)
      See Farm machinery
  - Agricultural labor.
    See Labor; see also 33-H
  - Agricultural pests, 1917-1918 (Folder 90: 19)
  - Agriculture, 1918. (Folder 90: 20)
    Includes "Graphic Summary of American Agriculture," from Yearbook of Department of Agriculture for 1915, by Middleton Smith.
  - Agriculture Department, 1917-1922 (Folder 90)
  - David F. Houston, United States Secretary of Agriculture, 1917-1919 (Folder 90-93: 1-12)
    - Annual Report of the Secretary of Agriculture, 1918 (Folder 91: 13)
    - Carl L. Alsberg, Chief of the Bureau of Chemistry, 1917-1918 (Folder 91: 14-15)
    - Floyd R. Harrison, 1917-1918 (Folder 91: 1-2)
    - Raymond A. Pearson, Assistant Secretary, 1917-1918 (Folder 92: 3)
    - Correspondence A-Z, 1917-1919 (Folder 92: 4-5)
    - Reports, 1917-1922 (Folder 92: 6)
    - Agricultural Production for 1918, report (Folder 92: 7)
    - Agricultural Situation for 1918, statements, parts I-XI (Folder 92: 8)
    - Crop Estimates Bureau monthly crop report, January 1917 - February 1919 (Folder 92: 9-12)
    - Markets Bureau, 1917-1919 (Folder 92)
    - Charles J. Brand, 1917-1918 (Folder 92: 13-15)
      - Food Survey, vol. I-II, 1918-1919 (Folder 92: 1-3)
      - War Emergency Food Survey, 1917-1918 (Folder 93: 4-5)
      - Rules and Regulations...under the Food Products Inspection Law of August 10, 1917 (Folder 93: 6)
      - Agriculture Department and Food Administration Monthly Survey as of 1 October 1918, by the Central Bureau of Planning and Statistics, War Industries Board (Folder 93: 7)
  - Alaska. (Folder 93)
    See 6-H
  - Alcohol, 1917-1918. (Folder : 8)
    See also 11-H; 29-H
  - Alcoholic beverages. (Folder 93)
    See Beer and liquor; Canada, Grain used in alcoholic beverages; Grain used in brewing; War Prohibition
  - Alfalfa meal.
    See Feeding stuffs
  - Algeria.
    See Africa
  - Alien enemies, 1917-1918. (Folder : 9)
    See also Internment camps, Noncombatants
  - Alien Property Custodian, 1918. (Folder 93: 10)
    See also Alien enemies, World Trade Board Enemy Trade Bureau
  - Alimentation. (Folder 93)
    See 11-H
  - Allen, Ben S.
    See 12-H (Books, Pamphlets, Reports)
  - Allen, Lloyd.
    See 12-H
  - Allen, Mrs. Lloyd (Alice).
  - Allied Food Council.
    See Inter-Allied Food Council in International Food Controls File
  - Allied Maritime Transport Council.
    See International Food Controls File
  - Allied Provisions Export Commission (APEC), 1917-1919
    - Minutes of meetings, 1917-1919 (Folder 93: 11)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 93: 12-14)
    - Index to British Ministry of Food cables, 1917-1918. (Folder 93: 1)
      See also 22-H
  - Allies, 1918 (Folder 94: 2)
  - Alsberg, Carl L. (Folder 94)
    See Agricultural Department
  - American Agricultural Commission, 1918-1919 (Folder : 3)
  - American Expeditionary Forces (AEF). (Folder 94)
    See Food parcels for soldiers, France-Sales of merchandise to Allied troops, Rations, Spain-War supplies, United States Army
  - American Federation of Labor, Samuel Gompers, President.
    See 33-H
  - American Food Journal, 1917 (Folder : 4)
  - American Red Cross, 1917-1918. (Folder 94)
    See also Italy, Reports
  - Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 94: 5-7)
  - Chairman Henry P. Davison, 1917-1918 (Folder 94: 8)
  - Ammonia. (Folder 94)
    See 11-H; 39-H; Exports, Ammonia and ammonia sulphate.
  - Amsden, Donna H., correspondence regarding Sugar Board and materials at Stanford Library, 1919-1920 (Folder : 9)
  - Anonymous letters, 1917-1918 (Folder 94: 10)
  - Argentina, 1917-1919 (Folder 94)
    - Agriculture, crops, and stocks, 1917-1919 (Folder 94: 11)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 94: 12)
    - Exports and imports, 1917-1918 (Folder 94: 13-14)
    - Labor troubles, 1917-1918 (Folder 94: 15)
    - Livestock and meat, 1917-1918 (Folder 94: 16)
    - Official Bulletin "Tree Luxburg Telegrams Only Withheld", December 21, 1917 (Folder 94: 17)
    - Purchase of wheat crop by France and Great Britain, 1917-1918 (Folder 94: 18)
  - Armour and Company. (Folder 94)
    See 15-H; Great Britain, Food Administration, Armour and Co.
  - Army camps.
    See Camps and cantonments
  - Army rations.
    See Rations, Army
  - Arnold, H. G.
    See 19-H
  - Arsenic.
    See Agricultural pests; 39-H
  - Atkins, Kroll & Co., 1917-1918 (Folder : 19)
  - Austin, Mary, National Arts Club, New York City, 1917 (Folder 94: 20)
  - Australia, 1914-1919. (Folder 94)
    See also New Zealand; Tasmania
    - Agriculture, 1918-1919 (Folder 94: 21)
    - Exports and imports, 1918-1919 (Folder 94: 1)
    - Legislation, 1914-1919 (Folder 95: 2-4)
    - Prices and price-fixing, 1914-1918 (Folder 95: 5)
  - Austria-Hungary, 1917-1919 (Folder 95)
    - Crops, Stocks, 1917-1918 (Folder 95: 6-7)
    - Food Ministry, 1917-1918 (Folder 95)
      - Dairy products, eggs, fats, and oils, 1918 (Folder 95: 8)
      - Fruits and vegetables, 1918 (Folder 95: 9)
      - Grain, flour, bread, and potatoes, 1918 (Folder 95: 10)
      - Livestock and meat, 1918 (Folder 95: 11)
      - Prices, 1918 (Folder 95: 12)
      - Rations, 1918 (Folder 95: 13)
      - Regulations, 1917-1918 (Folder 95: 14)
      - Requisitioning and sugar, 1918 (Folder 95: 15)
  - Aviation acts, 1917. (Folder 95: 16)
    See also War legislation
  - B correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 95: 17-18)
  - B correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 95: 1-12)
  - Babst, Earl D. (Folder 96)
    See 30-H; 48-H; Sugar
  - Bagg, Ether Mather.
    See 5-H
  - Bags.
    See Containers
  - Bahamas Islands.
    See British West Indies
  - Bailey, Thomas A., The Policy of the United States Toward Neutrals.
    See Neutrals
  - Baker, Newton D.
    See War Department
  - Baldwin, Roger S.
  - Balfour Mission.
    See State Department, Personnel of Foreign Missions